// src/questions/javaQuestions.js
const javaQuestions = [
    {
      question: "What is Java?",
      options: ["A programming language", "A type of coffee", "An island in Indonesia"],
      correctAnswer: "A programming language",
    },
    {
      question: "Which company developed Java?",
      options: ["Microsoft", "Sun Microsystems", "IBM"],
      correctAnswer: "Sun Microsystems",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the main purpose of Java Virtual Machine (JVM)?",
      options: ["To execute Java bytecode", "To compile Java code", "To manage Java databases"],
      correctAnswer: "To execute Java bytecode",
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is a feature of Java?",
      options: ["Multiple inheritance", "Pointers", "Manual memory management"],
      correctAnswer: "Multiple inheritance",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the use of 'final' keyword in Java?",
      options: ["To declare a variable constant", "To mark a class as final", "To create a final method"],
      correctAnswer: "To declare a variable constant",
    },
    {
      question: "What is an interface in Java?",
      options: ["A class with only static methods", "A way to achieve multiple inheritance", "A built-in data type"],
      correctAnswer: "A way to achieve multiple inheritance",
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is not a Java primitive data type?",
      options: ["int", "boolean", "string"],
      correctAnswer: "string",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the purpose of the 'super' keyword in Java?",
      options: ["To call the superclass method", "To create a new instance of a class", "To define a constant variable"],
      correctAnswer: "To call the superclass method",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the default value of a boolean variable in Java?",
      options: ["true", "false", "null"],
      correctAnswer: "false",
    },
    {
      question: "Which Java keyword is used to exit from a loop?",
      options: ["break", "exit", "terminate"],
      correctAnswer: "break",
    },
  ];
  
  export default javaQuestions;
  